<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laura on Pastel Cravings</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/authors/laura/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Laura on Pastel Cravings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 20:01:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/authors/laura/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Café Melbourne</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/cafemelbourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 20:01:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/cafemelbourne/</guid>
      <description>As you enter The Mile End, one of the hippest areas in Montreal, you’ll come across a quaint little brunch spot called Le Café Melbourne. First, you’ll notice a sign reading &amp;ldquo;Our French is not good, but our coffee is”, flash a grin, enter the café, and be greeted with the warm smiles of the Australian owner and his staff. Take a seat, and get ready for some Insta-worthy moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/topstudycafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 20:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/topstudycafe/</guid>
      <description>For this special post, I’ve asked my co-bloggers to list me all their top coffee places to study and I’ve assembled the ones that was in common on our lists.
Legend: &amp;hearts; = the bloggers’ favourites
1. La Finca Coffee &amp;amp; Office |&amp;hearts;Laura
|&amp;hearts;Trang
|ADDRESS: 1067 Rue de Bleury, Montréal, QC H2Z 1N1| Métro Place D’Armes
A favourite of mine because of the accessibility by metro, the coziness of the place and the instagrammy worth of everyshot and every angle !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Café Sfouf</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/cafesfouf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 22:32:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/cafesfouf/</guid>
      <description>In the past years, I’ve had my fair share of following the trend of the #MTLCafeCrawl. After much exploring (and many cups of coffee in my system), I can definitely say that the Café Sfouf has become one of my all-time favorite cafes in Montreal.
When I first stumbled across this cute little spot in the Gay Village, I was drawn to its vintage exterior and the welcoming atmosphere that it exuded.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>