<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drinks on Pastel Cravings</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/drinks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drinks on Pastel Cravings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 20:01:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/drinks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Café Melbourne</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/cafemelbourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 20:01:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/cafemelbourne/</guid>
      <description>As you enter The Mile End, one of the hippest areas in Montreal, you’ll come across a quaint little brunch spot called Le Café Melbourne. First, you’ll notice a sign reading &amp;ldquo;Our French is not good, but our coffee is”, flash a grin, enter the café, and be greeted with the warm smiles of the Australian owner and his staff. Take a seat, and get ready for some Insta-worthy moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Café Sfouf</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/cafesfouf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 22:32:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/cafesfouf/</guid>
      <description>In the past years, I’ve had my fair share of following the trend of the #MTLCafeCrawl. After much exploring (and many cups of coffee in my system), I can definitely say that the Café Sfouf has become one of my all-time favorite cafes in Montreal.
When I first stumbled across this cute little spot in the Gay Village, I was drawn to its vintage exterior and the welcoming atmosphere that it exuded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monopole Café</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/cafemonopole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 19:10:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/cafemonopole/</guid>
      <description>Monopole is a coffee shop, restaurant and {bar in the Cité du Multimédia, a neighbourhood consisting mostly of tech companies. It has been open since May 12th.
It has a nice selection of pastries and serves coffee from 49th Parallel and Bows and Arrows. It has quickly become my go-to coffee shop for commuting to work between Old Montreal and Griffintown. Lunch and dinner menus are also available with good quality food for reasonable prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Spoon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/spooncafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 10:10:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/spooncafe/</guid>
      <description>Whenever I&amp;rsquo;m at Guy Concordia or Peel and I find myself searching for a coffee shop, this one is the first to pop in my head. Very accessible by metro, it only took me 5 mins to walk to Crescent St and find this little jewel. I love the decor, immediately the combination of the green from the plants and the white modern look caught my eyes.
They have a cute little space window where you can work and look outside and it emanates the feel of a greenhouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kampai Garden</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/kampaigarden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 11:10:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/kampaigarden/</guid>
      <description>Kampai Garden was one the most popular place even before it opened its doors last summer. Why? Because everything in the restaurant screams Instagram! From neon lights in the wall, to the french sentence, to the plants giving that green vibe everywhere.
 Kampai menu is very unique . I went there for supper the first time, got me some beef sashimi, sweet potato fries and fried chicken. For my second time they offered Poke!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>