<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trang on Pastel Cravings</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/authors/trang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trang on Pastel Cravings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:06:46 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/authors/trang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyomi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/kyomi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:06:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/kyomi/</guid>
      <description>When you step in the restaurant, it&amp;rsquo;s like entering a whole new world (believe me, you can&amp;rsquo;t tell from outside). The decor screams romantic and modern asian fusion. It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect place to bring in your date or a family gathering.
I ordered the Salmon Tartare (meal version comes with sweet potatoes so why not?! :D) AND THIS RIGHT HERE IS HEAVEN. It&amp;rsquo;s sweet and light, the asian inspiration crispy crackers go very well with this tartare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kumamoto Ramen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/kumamoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:06:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/kumamoto/</guid>
      <description>When I heard about this new ramen place in town, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier. Because more ramen is always good.
What&amp;rsquo;s cool about this new restaurant is the isolation booth concept. You have these wood panels separating you and you neighbors. You have a little button for ordering food and an autorefill water system.Then you receive your bowl of ramen through a curtain covered window.
Unique Ramen I ordered a Black Tonkotsu Ramen and it was so savoury and delicious!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/topstudycafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 20:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/topstudycafe/</guid>
      <description>For this special post, I’ve asked my co-bloggers to list me all their top coffee places to study and I’ve assembled the ones that was in common on our lists.
Legend: &amp;hearts; = the bloggers’ favourites
1. La Finca Coffee &amp;amp; Office |&amp;hearts;Laura
|&amp;hearts;Trang
|ADDRESS: 1067 Rue de Bleury, Montréal, QC H2Z 1N1| Métro Place D’Armes
A favourite of mine because of the accessibility by metro, the coziness of the place and the instagrammy worth of everyshot and every angle !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Spoon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/spooncafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 10:10:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/spooncafe/</guid>
      <description>Whenever I&amp;rsquo;m at Guy Concordia or Peel and I find myself searching for a coffee shop, this one is the first to pop in my head. Very accessible by metro, it only took me 5 mins to walk to Crescent St and find this little jewel. I love the decor, immediately the combination of the green from the plants and the white modern look caught my eyes.
They have a cute little space window where you can work and look outside and it emanates the feel of a greenhouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crew Café</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/crewcollective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 11:10:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/crewcollective/</guid>
      <description>1. The Classiest Spot in Town Yes, you read it right. The classiest. Crew Collective Café is one of the most eye-candy coffee shop in our city, a main tourist attraction too. The building was once a bank and now they use the beautiful building design to turn it into a coffee shop and now also a lounge club (La Voute).
2. The Neighborhood and Accessibility Situated in the heart of the most elegant neighborhood in town, close to Metro Square Victoria (2 mins walk) and in front of te World Trade Center Montreal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kampai Garden</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/kampaigarden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 11:10:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/kampaigarden/</guid>
      <description>Kampai Garden was one the most popular place even before it opened its doors last summer. Why? Because everything in the restaurant screams Instagram! From neon lights in the wall, to the french sentence, to the plants giving that green vibe everywhere.
 Kampai menu is very unique . I went there for supper the first time, got me some beef sashimi, sweet potato fries and fried chicken. For my second time they offered Poke!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizzeria No.900</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/pizza900/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 10:24:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/pizza900/</guid>
      <description>Once you enter the place, you will notice the coziness of the entrance. However, it’s only an illusion since they have more seats behind.
I ordered a Margherita Pizza (9$) and my boyfriend got the Italian Sausage (13$). The crust was perfect, not too dry, a little chewy and soft in the center. Tomato sauce was okay but what really amazes me was … THE CHEESE, miam ! &amp;lt;3
They also happen to have an open window counter which is ideal for summer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>